[
    {
        "node": "1",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467725",
        "longitude": "-2.234169",
        "coords": "53.46774654645258, -2.234214450492013",
        "altitude": "104",
        "links": {
            "front": "2"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "2",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467833",
        "longitude": "-2.233947",
        "coords": "53.467738792063095, -2.2342052552726916",
        "altitude": "141",
        "links": {
            "right": "3",
            "front": "5"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "3",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467833",
        "longitude": "-2.233947",
        "coords": "53.467729213109415, -2.234196826321646",
        "altitude": "141",
        "links": {
            "right": "4",
            "left": "2"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "4",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467833",
        "longitude": "-2.233947",
        "coords": "53.46771917801279, -2.234224411979612",
        "altitude": "141",
        "links": {
            "left": "3"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "5",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467833",
        "longitude": "-2.233947",
        "coords": "53.46771507274529, -2.2341960600533697",
        "altitude": "141",
        "links": {
            "front": "6"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "6",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467833",
        "longitude": "-2.233947",
        "coords": "53.46770594992722, -2.2341807346878326",
        "altitude": "141",
        "links": {
            "right": "7",
            "left": "9",
            "front": "10"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "7",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467833",
        "longitude": "-2.233947",
        "coords": "53.46769865167136, -2.2341769033464485",
        "altitude": "141",
        "links": {
            "right": "8",
            "left": "6"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "8",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467833",
        "longitude": "-2.233947",
        "coords": "53.46769956395343, -2.2341837997609404",
        "altitude": "141",
        "links": {
            "left": "7",
            "front": "35"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "9",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467833",
        "longitude": "-2.233947",
        "coords": "53.46773736005993, -2.234179708605646",
        "altitude": "141",
        "links": {
            "right": "6"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "10",
        "floor": "1",
        "coords": "53.467726183488566, -2.2341770263967358",
        "altitude": "141",
        "links": {
            "right": "11",
            "left": "13",
            "front": "14",
            "back": "6"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "11",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467833",
        "longitude": "-2.233947",
        "coords": "53.46769105710229, -2.2341669681133243",
        "altitude": "141",
        "links": {
            "left": "10",
            "right": "12"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "12",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467833",
        "longitude": "-2.233947",
        "coords": "53.467682275501204, -2.234218600634837",
        "altitude": "141",
        "links": {
            "left": "11"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "13",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467833",
        "longitude": "-2.233947",
        "coords": "53.467696853622975, -2.2341509401566366",
        "altitude": "141",
        "links": {
            "right": "10"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "14",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467833",
        "longitude": "-2.233947",
        "coords": "53.46768439348145, -2.2341367606147036",
        "altitude": "141",
        "links": {
            "back": "10",
            "right": "15",
            "front": "16"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "15",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467833",
        "longitude": "-2.233947",
        "coords": "53.467677560499034, -2.2341543162380493",
        "altitude": "141",
        "links": {
            "left": "14"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "16",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467833",
        "longitude": "-2.233947",
        "coords": "53.467677560499034, -2.234121905856487",
        "altitude": "141",
        "links": {
            "left": "17",
            "back": "14",
            "right": "18",
            "front": "19"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "17",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467833",
        "longitude": "-2.233947",
        "coords": "53.46766871781432, -2.2341043502331406",
        "altitude": "141",
        "links": {
            "right": "16"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "18",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467833",
        "longitude": "-2.233947",
        "coords": "53.46765517486002, -2.2341281894577425",
        "altitude": "141",
        "links": {
            "left": "17"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "19",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467833",
        "longitude": "-2.233947",
        "coords": "53.46766158300979, -2.234119731242122",
        "altitude": "141",
        "links": {
            "back": "16",
            "right": "20",
            "left": "27",
            "front": "26"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "20",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467833",
        "longitude": "-2.233947",
        "coords": "53.46765242850769, -2.2341412612428324",
        "altitude": "141",
        "links": {
            "front": "21",
            "left": "19"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "21",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467833",
        "longitude": "-2.233947",
        "coords": "53.46764785125594, -2.234166635886527",
        "altitude": "141",
        "links": {
            "right": "22",
            "left": "23"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "22",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467609",
        "longitude": "-2.234218",
        "coords": "53.46765151305739, -2.2341674048151234",
        "altitude": "90",
        "links": {
            "left": "21",
            "front": "24"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "23",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467833",
        "longitude": "-2.233947",
        "coords": "53.46763869675089, -2.2341412612428324",
        "altitude": "141",
        "links": {
            "right": "21",
            "front": "25",
            "left": "26"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "24",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467833",
        "longitude": "-2.233947",
        "coords": "53.467602078710954, -2.2341051215987826",
        "altitude": "141",
        "links": {
            "back": "22"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "25",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467619",
        "longitude": "-2.234181",
        "coords": "53.467594755099185, -2.2340989701700087",
        "altitude": "90",
        "links": {
            "back": "23",
            "left": "26",
            "right": "47"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "26",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467619",
        "longitude": "-2.234181",
        "coords": "53.467602078710954, -2.23407205766912",
        "altitude": "90",
        "links": {
            "right": "25",
            "front": "28"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "27",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467833",
        "longitude": "-2.233947",
        "coords": "53.46760390961369, -2.234041300525248",
        "altitude": "141",
        "links": {
            "right": "19"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "28",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467619",
        "longitude": "-2.234181",
        "coords": "53.46760574051639, -2.2340659062403456",
        "altitude": "90",
        "links": {
            "back": "26",
            "right": "29"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "29",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467619",
        "longitude": "-2.234181",
        "coords": "53.46759658600226, -2.2340466830254258",
        "altitude": "90",
        "links": {
            "left": "28",
            "right": "30",
            "front": "31",
            "back": "26"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "30",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467619",
        "longitude": "-2.234181",
        "coords": "53.46758239650147, -2.2340674440975397",
        "altitude": "90",
        "links": {
            "left": "29"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "31",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467630",
        "longitude": "-2.234132",
        "coords": "53.467583769679166, -2.2340251530247155",
        "altitude": "90",
        "links": {
            "back": "29",
            "left": "32",
            "right": "33",
            "front": "34"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "32",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467630",
        "longitude": "-2.234132",
        "coords": "53.4675869737603, -2.234018232667344",
        "altitude": "90",
        "links": {
            "right": "31"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "33",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467630",
        "longitude": "-2.234132",
        "coords": "53.46756042565216, -2.234026690881909",
        "altitude": "90",
        "links": {
            "left": "31"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "34",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467630",
        "longitude": "-2.234132",
        "coords": "53.46755264430697, -2.23399747159523",
        "altitude": "90",
        "links": {
            "back": "31"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "35",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467705",
        "longitude": "-2.234124",
        "coords": "53.46766799116006, -2.234212002673738",
        "altitude": "90",
        "links": {
            "back": "8",
            "left": "36",
            "front": "37"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "36",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467705",
        "longitude": "-2.234124",
        "coords": "53.46768630015555, -2.234192779458818",
        "altitude": "90",
        "links": {
            "right": "35"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "37",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467705",
        "longitude": "-2.234124",
        "coords": "53.46766295618493, -2.234205082316367",
        "altitude": "90",
        "links": {
            "back": "35",
            "right": "38"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "38",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467705",
        "longitude": "-2.234124",
        "coords": "53.46765055950166, -2.234272798715087",
        "altitude": "90",
        "links": {
            "left": "37",
            "front": "39",
            "right": "40"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "39",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467697",
        "longitude": "-2.234272",
        "coords": "53.467645974311026, -2.2342751095016946",
        "altitude": "90",
        "links": {
            "back": "38",
            "left": "41"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "40",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467697",
        "longitude": "-2.234272",
        "coords": "53.46767486100371, -2.2342481503246105",
        "altitude": "90",
        "links": {
            "left": "38"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "41",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467697",
        "longitude": "-2.234272",
        "coords": "53.467637720966664, -2.234249690849016",
        "altitude": "90",
        "links": {
            "right": "39",
            "back": "42",
            "front": "43"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "42",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467697",
        "longitude": "-2.234272",
        "coords": "53.46765789580563, -2.2342689474040753",
        "altitude": "90",
        "links": {
            "front": "41"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "43",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467697",
        "longitude": "-2.234272",
        "coords": "53.46763359429388, -2.234223501934134",
        "altitude": "90",
        "links": {
            "back": "41",
            "left": "44",
            "right": "45",
            "front": "46"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "44",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467697",
        "longitude": "-2.234272",
        "coords": "53.46762029723437, -2.234176515939787",
        "altitude": "90",
        "links": {
            "right": "43"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "45",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467697",
        "longitude": "-2.234272",
        "coords": "53.46761846315688, -2.234252001635623",
        "altitude": "90",
        "links": {
            "left": "43"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "46",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467697",
        "longitude": "-2.234272",
        "coords": "53.46758453270886, -2.234153408073715",
        "altitude": "90",
        "links": {
            "back": "43",
            "left": "47",
            "right": "48"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "47",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467697",
        "longitude": "-2.234272",
        "coords": "53.467574903793015, -2.234143394665084",
        "altitude": "90",
        "links": {
            "right": "46",
            "left": "25"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "48",
        "floor": "1",
        "latitude": "53.467697",
        "longitude": "-2.234272",
        "coords": "53.467560689675125, -2.2341988535436568",
        "altitude": "90",
        "links": {
            "left": "46"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "1",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.46763301434787, -2.2342208931714063",
        "links": {
            "left": "2"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "2",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.467613418127655, -2.2342081501386817",
        "links": {
            "right": "1",
            "front": "3"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "3",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.46762163589854, -2.234164611443539",
        "links": {
            "back": "2",
            "front": "4"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "4",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.467573642919696, -2.234301345117739",
        "links": {
            "back": "3",
            "left": "5",
            "right": "6",
            "front": "7"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "5",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.4675810825982, -2.234244536796791",
        "links": {
            "right": "4"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "6",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.46759866728765, -2.234336566276727",
        "links": {
            "left": "4"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "7",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.4675682322436, -2.2342990727849013",
        "links": {
            "back": "4",
            "left": "8",
            "right": "9",
            "front": "10"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "8",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.467554029215584, -2.234309298282672",
        "links": {
            "right": "7"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "9",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.467596638285414, -2.23431157061551",
        "links": {
            "left": "7"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "10",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.467551479060305, -2.2343135274522865",
        "links": {
            "back": "7",
            "left": "11"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "11",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.46752821429324, -2.23427899715245",
        "links": {
            "right": "10",
            "left": "12",
            "front": "32"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "12",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.467547153084176, -2.2342710433954505",
        "links": {
            "right": "10",
            "front": "14"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "13",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.46756609186666, -2.234241879619785",
        "links": {
            "right": "10"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "14",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.46754241838724, -2.23424585649828435",
        "links": {
            "back": "12",
            "front": "15"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "15",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.46754636396805, -2.2342127158441194",
        "links": {
            "back": "14",
            "left": "16",
            "right": "17",
            "front": "18"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "16",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.46755662247647, -2.2342312746104516",
        "links": {
            "back": "14",
            "right": "15"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "17",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.46752821429324, -2.234211390217953",
        "links": {
            "left": "17",
            "right": "15"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "18",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.46756135717182, -2.234162342049788",
        "links": {
            "left": "19",
            "back": "15",
            "front": "21",
            "right": "20"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "19",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.46757871771695, -2.234167644554454",
        "links": {
            "right": "18"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "20",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.467592132678774, -2.234207413339453",
        "links": {
            "left": "18"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "21",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.46756530275089, -2.234137155152622",
        "links": {
            "back": "20",
            "left": "22",
            "right": "23"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "22",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.467583452409855, -2.2341451089096216",
        "links": {
            "right": "21",
            "front": "24"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "23",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.467558989824205, -2.234130527021789",
        "links": {
            "left": "21"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "24",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.46759607825497, -2.234150411414288",
        "links": {
            "back": "22",
            "front": "25"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "25",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.46762685373676, -2.234111968255456",
        "links": {
            "back": "24",
            "front": "26"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "26",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.46762969681429, -2.2341169540635377",
        "links": {
            "right": "27",
            "back": "25",
            "left": "28",
            "front": "29"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "27",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.46762770099312, -2.2341035430189895",
        "links": {
            "left": "26"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "28",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.467622112693356, -2.234125000690267",
        "links": {
            "right": "26"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "29",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.46764047424693, -2.2341243301380396",
        "links": {
            "back": "26",
            "left": "30",
            "right": "31"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "30",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.46762450768029, -2.2341625516177896",
        "links": {
            "right": "29"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "31",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.46764845752981, -2.2340794031415885",
        "links": {
            "left": "29",
            "front": "48"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "32",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.46752299538414, -2.2342769070531756",
        "links": {
            "back": "11",
            "front": "33"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "33",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.46752551482282, -2.234279898256644",
        "links": {
            "back": "32",
            "front": "34"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "34",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.46745821102887, -2.2342211647185524",
        "links": {
            "back": "33",
            "left": "35",
            "right": "36",
            "front": "37"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "35",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.4674734853977, -2.23417692477085",
        "links": {
            "right": "34"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "36",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.46741660151346, -2.2342008143426093",
        "links": {
            "left": "34"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "37",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.46742028843418, -2.234178694368758",
        "links": {
            "back": "34",
            "left": "38",
            "front": "39"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "38",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.4674223952459, -2.234116758441974",
        "links": {
            "right": "37"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "39",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.467367419618476, -2.2341290490114667",
        "links": {
            "back": "37",
            "left": "40",
            "right": "41",
            "front": "42"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "40",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.46738859489172, -2.234096823206375",
        "links": {
            "back": "37",
            "right": "39"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "41",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.4673808667954, -2.2341557427915757",
        "links": {
            "left": "39"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "42",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.46732914796073, -2.2340858381989652",
        "links": {
            "back": "39",
            "left": "43",
            "right": "44",
            "front": "45"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "43",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.46736778847536, -2.2340498872656225",
        "links": {
            "right": "42"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "44",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.467351143334895, -2.234142760510091",
        "links": {
            "left": "42"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "45",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.467313097275074, -2.2340848395619277",
        "links": {
            "back": "42",
            "front": "46"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "46",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.46729882999387, -2.2340778491026665",
        "links": {
            "back": "45",
            "right": "47"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "47",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.46731071939522, -2.2340299145248763",
        "links": {
            "back": "45",
            "left": "46"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "48",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.46764302682141, -2.234113800042945",
        "links": {
            "back": "31",
            "front": "49"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "49",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.46766086077757, -2.2340428968132966",
        "links": {
            "back": "48",
            "left": "50",
            "right": "51",
            "front": "52"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "50",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.4676804781207, -2.234057876368856",
        "links": {
            "right": "49"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "51",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.46765372719601, -2.2340329104429237",
        "links": {
            "left": "49"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "52",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.46770247331282, -2.233956015391051",
        "links": {
            "back": "49",
            "left": "54",
            "right": "53",
            "front": "55"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "53",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.4676810725855, -2.2339869731392077",
        "links": {
            "left": "52"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "54",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.4677096068862, -2.2340099417910655",
        "links": {
            "right": "52"
        }
    },
    {
        "node": "55",
        "floor": "2",
        "coords": "53.46771079581497, -2.2339390385614175",
        "links": {
            "back": "52"
        }
    }
]